How do you like it?
Does it look good?
Perfect.
It's just
tailor-made for you.
Qianqian likes this perfume very much.
I'll give it to you as a return gift.
It's so precious.
You'd better keep it for yourself.
It's okay.
My brother-in-law also likes the smell.
You can spray it before going to bed.
After all, its smell
is quite attractive.
Sister Qianqian,
it's time.
I'm going to the company.
I like the clothes you gave me.
Thank you.
Have you been to Singapore?
It's so late to come to me.
Aren't you afraid of being late for the press conference tomorrow?
Let's go.
I know a chef
who makes great sashimi.
The press conference will start in ten minutes.
The process list
is on your desk.
Got it.
Aren't you afraid of the press conference being held at the scene?
Are you?
I dare to go into the tiger's den.
I'm not afraid of the cameras downstairs.
[Your prey is the reporters downstairs.]
[If your shirt gets covered in lipstick,]
[tomorrow's headlines will be juicy.]
Thank you all for coming.
Today,
Golden Thread will start a new chapter.
The Dark Fairy Tale series
will debut globally
at next month's
fashion show.
Now,
let's welcome the chief designer of this series,
Ms. Jiang Li.
Welcome to this media meeting.
I am Jiang Li, the chief designer of Dark Fairy Tale.
Dark Fairy Tale aims to tear apart the sugar-coated fairy tales.
We use spider-web lace...
We use spider-web lace
to interpret betrayal.
Broken crystal
pieced together ambition.
For example, this one,
the poisoned apple of Snow White.
Every stitch
embodies a lie from now on.
To add,
in the series,
there are also Cinderella's crystal instruments.
At midnight,
what's left
is not only the shoes,
but also the naked truth
[the naked truth.]
How much do you need?
Just fill it in yourself.
You're so generous.
But how do you know about
my private deal with Zhuang Wan?
Actually, the Shen family
is more complicated than you think.
I've already noticed it when you
proposed an alliance with my sister-in-law.
Grandpa doesn't think highly of the future of Golden Thread,
so he doesn't want to get involved in it.
What she did was her own will.
She can't
give you
what you want.
But I
can.
I've heard of your cautious investment style.
But why do you trust me?
The Shen Family
invests in companies,
but I invest in people.
I'm not here representing the Shen Family's interests.
Aren't you afraid I'll lose everything
and you'll get nothing?
Interest is like this glass of sparkling water.
The bubbles that boil on the surface
are often just superficial.
The truth that lies at the bottom of the glass is
you
need my investment.
Mutual exploitation is the best alliance.
Even if I don't win,
I believe I won't lose.
Young Master Shen is so bold.
But Ms. Jiang,
can you answer me a question seriously?
What question?
What you said at the convenience store that day,
what you said at the convenience store?
It's you!
As Zhou Jian's personal assistant,
you stole my clothes
and jewelry.
You thought I wouldn't notice?
Mr. Lu,
I'm sorry.
I won't do it again.
I just saw some of your clothes and shoes
were thrown away or given away after one use.
So I...
You fixed the shoes,
why did you buy a new pair?
Because you were afraid I would find out.
You...
You are...
Zi
Man
Teng.
That day,
you just went to the studio to finish the painting.
But I didn't expect that
I would be in the family building of chemical fiber factory.
You were in a hurry to escape,
but because you were too anxious,
you broke the heel of the high heels you stole from me.
Because you didn't have time to take the broken heel,
you were afraid that I would find out everything you did.
So,
you found a shoemaker
to make a replica of the heel
and fixed the high heels.
As Zhou Jian's personal assistant,
you had access to our home.
While I was away,
you slipped into the dressing room
and replaced the repaired shoes.
You just waited for me to throw them away,
then you could cover everything up.
But you didn't expect
that I wore these shoes
when I went to Singapore.
You know that
the repair of the shoes
will leave traces.
Finally, you used up all your savings
to buy a new pair.
Tell me.
What's the story about the painting
that looks like Su Muchen?
Mr. Lu,
do you really think
I am Purple Vine?
Are you not?
You're right.
But not entirely.
I'm the Purple Vine who sells paintings.
But the person who painted these paintings
is the woman Mr. Zhou can never forget.
Su
Mu
Chen
Impossible.
Su Muchen has been dead for a long time.
Hello?
Have you decided?
Just give me enough to disappear.
I'm willing to tell you everything I know.
Okay.
What I need is the news that can pin down Annie,
not the rumor.
The news I give you
can destroy the entire Lu family.
Name your price.
Five hundred million.
I'll buy 14% of your shares.
The market value of the shares is two billion.
Are you kidding?
You've lost your friendship and family.
Isn't it worth
to exchange 14% of the shares
for the remaining love?
Or do you want your brother-in-law to know
that your reputation
is just an empty check?
You're threatening me.
No one will believe
what Dean Li said.
Then why are you negotiating with me here?
Why don't you force me to leave
like you used to?
Why don't you confront Annie?
Because you're scared.
You're afraid that things will get worse
after confirming with Annie.
After all, Annie adopted you
just to nibble away the shares left by the elder Mr. Lu.
When you are no longer useful,
Annie can't be your backer,
and brother-in-law will abandon you without hesitation.
You planned it all.
You used my friendship with you
to realize your plan.
Friendship?
Don't say "use" so nicely.
Do we really have a friendship?
I'm just a weed that you look down on and laugh at.
Have you ever thought about
how Annie got to where she is today?
You...
This is to return the meeting gift you gave me last time.
I'll give you time to think it through.
But I want to remind you.
You even lost the love you got by any means necessary.
When Annie dilutes your shares completely,
you won't have any chips.
you won't be able to provide a comfortable life for Mumu.
After all, for Annie,
he's just the child of you and Zhou Jian.
Zhou Jian was already married before he joined the Lu family.
He had an affair?
Yes.
You're really smart, Mr. Shen.
Lu Qianqian met Zhou Jian
after he joined the company.
And Lu Qianqian
got pregnant by Zhou Jian while he was still married.
Then why hasn't anyone
mentioned this matter for so many years?
Because Annie dealt with it personally.
She silenced everyone who knew about it with money.
Let me tell you,
just based on this information,
you have to give me a red envelope.
I spent twice the money
to get it from the people who knew.
That means
Zhou Jian's ex-wife
is Su Muchen,
Su Muli's sister.
Yes.
For some reason,
they haven't been in touch for a long time.
Even Zhou Jian doesn't know
that Su Muchen has a sister.
How did Su Muchen die?
She died in a car accident five years ago.
She was so sad to know that Zhou Jian
cheated on her,
so she drank that day.
Unfortunately, she was hit by a speeding truck
when she was crossing the road.
Well.
Did anyone else know about the things
I asked you to investigate?
Don't worry.
Okay.
Is this your revenge?
Su Mulan.
Senior.
Sister.
I'm sorry
for being late.
But I promise
soon
those who hurt you
will kneel here
and confess to you.